Class of 1941 Records, 1937-2003
Smith College Archives
Class of 1941 Records
1937-2003
Smith College. Class of 1941.
RG 80 UUID:20077694-fff1-4949-93a4-1dd510cd19b9
7 boxes (5.2 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1941.
The Class of 1941 was the sixty-third graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1941 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1941, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, questionnaires, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1941 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1941 (Box 2125, Folder 1)
- Commencement Dramatics 1941 (Box 2125, Folder 2)
- Commencement Photographs 1941 (Box 2125, Folder 3)
- Commencement Speaker 1941 (Box 2125, Folder 4)
- Freshman Handbook 1937-1938 (Box 2125, Folder 5)
- General 1939 (Box 2125, Folder 6)
- Groups 1937-1941 (Box 2125, Folder 7)
- Hoop Rolling 1941 (Box 2125, Folder 8)
- Ivy Day 1941 (Box 2125, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1941 (Box 2125, Folder 10)
- Junior Prom 1940 (Box 2125, Folder 11)
- Junior Prom-Garden Party 1940 (Box 2125, Folder 12)
- Junior Ushers 1940 (Box 2125, Folder 13)
- Last Sing 1941 (Box 2125, Folder 14)
- Class Letters 1967-2003 (Box 2125, Folder 15)
- Officers (Box 2126, Folder 1)
- Rally Day 1941 (Box 2126, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1942 (Box 2126, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1951 (Box 2126, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1956 (Box 2126, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1961 (Box 2126, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1966 (Box 2126, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1971 (Box 2126, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1976-1986 (Box 2126, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1991 (Box 2126, Folder 10)
- Reunions-Scrapbook 1991 (Box 2126, Folder 11)
- Reunions 2001 (Box 2126, Folder 12)
- Songs undated (Box 2126, Folder 13)
- Sophomore Carnival 1939 (Box 2126, Folder 14)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1939 (Box 2126, Folder 15)
- Class Supper 1941 (Box 2126, Folder 16)
- Year Book 1941 (Box 2126, Folder 17)
- Reunion Questionnaire: A-F 1991 (Box 2127, Folder 1)
- Reunion Questionnaire: F-N 1991 (Box 2127, Folder 2)
- Reunion Questionnaire: N-Z 1991 (Box 2127, Folder 3)